Clayton Reardon

Redondo Beach, CA | (424)-444-9490 | ClaytonReardon@gmail.com | Github

INTRO

I began my career in cybersecurity through hands-on experience with the penetration testing playground, HackTheBox, initially as a hobby, subsequently as a passion. Holding CompTIA Security+, Microsoft Azure Fundamentals and Administration certifications, I've expanded my expertise through various home-lab projects and Azure Cloud implementations, all documented on my GitHub. I am excited to continue to learn and grow in this field, undertake more projects, hack more boxes, and discover more of the many niches tech has to offer. While my focus is on offensive security, I am also entirely open to the possibility that a different sector will catch my eye.

CERTIFICATIONS

Microsoft - Azure Administration

Use the Microsoft Azure Portal, Bash CLI, and Powershell to:

- Identity Management and Governance: Manage Azure Identities and governance, including managing access and privileges for users and groups, as well as integration with external directories
- **Implement and Manage Storage:** Implement storage solutions such as blob storage, file storage, and configuring access policies for cloud, and hybrid scenarios
- Deploy and Manage Compute Resources: Deploy, configure, and manage virtual machines to meet the needs of various applications, workloads, and budgets
- Implement and Manage Virtual Networking: Implement and manage virtual networking including virtual networks, subnets, and network security groups to ensure secure and efficient network infrastructure
- **Monitor and Maintain Azure Resources:** Use various Azure tools to monitor and maintain Azure resources to track and maintain performance, monitor resources, and troubleshoot issues

Verify:

-https://learn.microsoft.com/api/credentials/share/en-us/ClaytonReardon-5708/60E89529BCC7B1D3?s haringId=D892AEAB21B31F63

Microsoft - Azure Fundamentals

Verify:

— https://learn.microsoft.com/api/credentials/share/en-us/ClaytonReardon-5708/1A5B9E557226A55E?s haringId=D892AEAB21B31F63

CompTIA - Security+

- **Identify Security Threats and Vulnerabilities:** Understand and identify various types of attacks, threats, and vulnerabilities, as well as the steps necessary to mitigate them
- **Implement Network Security:** Configuring and managing network infrastructure using technology and devices such as firewalls, VPNs, virtual networks, load balancers, and wireless security protocols, etc.
- Cryptography: Knowledge of cryptographic standards, practices, and use cases for securing and

- authenticating communication and data
- **Identity and Access Management:** Ability to implement access control policies and identity management to protect data and manage user privileges and access
- **Risk Management:** Understanding of various risk management frameworks and the ability to conduct security assessments to identify and mitigate risks
- **Compliance and Operational Security:** Awareness of legal and regulatory compliance mandates related to IT security, along with best practices for organization security
- Verify at: http://verify.compTIA.org | Code: RZZK3GHSHJB41YGR

EXPERIENCE

Home Lab

One of my main hobbies is setting up different tech projects at home.

- FileSharing and Database Website: I set up a website hosted in Azure that utilizes Azure
 functions to upload files to blob storage and generate SAS URLs. Depending on the contents of
 the file, a series of logic checks will be checked, and a virtual network containing various subnets
 and virtual machines will be automatically deployed using ARM templates. The website also
 utilizes another Azure function to interact with an SQL database to place orders and update store
 inventory. A CI/CD pipeline is set up using a Github Workflow. The writeup can be found on my
 Github
- Networking Infrastructure: I set up Azure networking infrastructure implementing dual virtual networks, integrating services such as VMs, load balancers, Azure Bastion, and Recovery Services Vault, across multiple subnets. Utilized a Site-to-Site VPN and networking peering to allow access from my local network. Utilized Azure VMs for web hosting integrated with an SQL servier, and a backend load balancer. Implemented Azure Bastion to allow secure access to the networks, and a Recovery Services Vault for data security. The writeup can be found on my Github.
- **IoT Device simulation and monitoring:** I set up an Azure IoT Hub and simulated multiple devices and telemetry. Routed data to Azure Stream and Log Analytics for data monitoring. I also sent data to a Power BI workspace for powerful real-time data visualization. Implemented alerts and action groups to notify administrators when certain conditions are met. The writeup of this project can be found on my Github.
- Azure Powered Resume: I've set up a website hosted on Azure to showcase my resume. It uses a CosmosDB instance to monitor page views. The writeup can be found on my Github.

HackTheBox

An offensive security playground. It's a ton of fun and a great resource.

- A link to writeups I've created describing techniques, methodology and the process behind cracking various systems can be found here.
- Requires problem solving, out of the box thinking, persistence, and "jack of all trades" knowledge, you have to learn a little bit about many technologies
- The community of individuals looking to help and give back to the infosec community is invaluable, and I try to do my part to help newer users. My forum account can be found here.

Barista 01/2022 - Present

Company: Starbucks

 After deciding to transition away from the music industry, I got an in between job at Starbucks to decide what to pursue next

- Efficient communication and teamwork were essential for a productive and enjoyable work experience
- Functioned in a fast-paced, quick turn around work environment

Audio Engineer/ Video Editor 09/2020 - 01/2022

Company: Spitfire Recording Studios

- Assisted Lead Engineer in setting up studio for bands and performers
- Assisted Lead Engineer is producing and mixing recorded music
- Edited video for the studio's youtube channel, Produce Like a Pro. https://www.youtube.com/@Producelikeapro

Audio Engineer 09/2019 - 03/2020

Company: Harmony Event Productions

- Set up staging, lighting, and sound for live events such as concerts and conferences
- Responsible for live mix to ensure sound quality for the performer and the audience

EDUCATION

Bachelor's in Advanced Audio Engineering

Los Angeles Recording Connection, 2019

VOLUNTEER & SUPPORT ROLES

Sponsor

Extensive experience providing one-on-one guidance and support within the framework of confidential recovery programs, offering personalized assistance to individuals navigating the path of recovery and fostering a supportive and non-judgmental environment to promote personal growth and adherence to the principles of anonymity.